Overriding config with .\config\train_shakespeare_optimal_iter10000.py:
# Baseline configuration
out_dir = 'out-shakespeare-iter10000'
eval_interval = 250
eval_iters = 200
log_interval = 10
always_save_checkpoint = False
wandb_log = False
wandb_project = 'nanoGPT-assignment'
wandb_run_name = 'iter10000'
dataset = 'shakespeare_char'
gradient_accumulation_steps = 1
batch_size = 64
block_size = 256
n_layer = 6
n_head = 6
n_embd = 384
dropout = 0.1
learning_rate = 5e-4
max_iters = 10000
lr_decay_iters = 10000
min_lr = 1e-4
beta2 = 0.99
warmup_iters = 100
weight_decay = 1e-1
device = 'cuda' # change to 'cuda' if you have a GPU
compile = False # set True only on Linux with GPU
Overriding: num_samples = 3
number of parameters: 10.65M
Loading meta from data\shakespeare_char\meta.pkl...


All the bride will be loaded made the way
Of the gravest call and bar their uses
That bar dilicaties with my faces' company.

YORK:
My friend is this now in a grief,
Even in this maids virtue, and long in leving
Well in a wall thumb on him.

DUKE VINCENTIO:
Hold, then, fool, live with his soldiers,
And in his death base of my crown,
And him compose off him the king to the fire;
And he must not know him for his son.
So much his brother discorr'd by his grace?

ISABELLA:
A very replain for for hi
---------------

Men pardon, my lord, will you have had embrace your blows
With tax your country. You were I behind
The flowers of castlements as for alliance,
Your deeds silver and parts to desire it;
Your voices and bear Richard: there is my
Turning to loud the wars of your holy kinsman's
About you see why burn and despected and cross,
The shore, holding and parting not with thee,
But to this determinest eyes and in roar'd with that
Hath sometimely like to the hand of Marcius that it
Whose is nothing excels he
---------------

MARIANA:
I beseech you, my lord; I warrant you how her heart;
That you were such a month of virtues and ends
Sincidents to his victory.

AUTOLYCUS:
Well, I beseech you.

Clown:
I come of you any in this blame at my breast.

AUTOLYCUS:
I have been to bear the commodicil hangs to me;
If I protest of thee the baby of the crown's death,
And see this is comfort lover doth him unto your feet.

AUTOLYCUS:
No, no more, my voice.

ISABELLA:
I take him of you.

Clown:
What! what say you to the Tower?

LUC
---------------
