Overriding config with .\config\train_shakespeare_optimal_iter1000.py:
# Baseline configuration
out_dir = 'out-shakespeare-iter1000'
eval_interval = 250
eval_iters = 200
log_interval = 10
always_save_checkpoint = False
wandb_log = False
wandb_project = 'nanoGPT-assignment'
wandb_run_name = 'iter1000'
dataset = 'shakespeare_char'
gradient_accumulation_steps = 1
batch_size = 64
block_size = 256
n_layer = 6
n_head = 6
n_embd = 384
dropout = 0.1
learning_rate = 5e-4
max_iters = 1000
lr_decay_iters = 1000
min_lr = 1e-4
beta2 = 0.99
warmup_iters = 100
weight_decay = 1e-1
device = 'cuda' # change to 'cuda' if you have a GPU
compile = False # set True only on Linux with GPU
Overriding: num_samples = 3
number of parameters: 10.65M
Loading meta from data\shakespeare_char\meta.pkl...

And they brids with the sons of a senators,
And will a mind talk him on this unquestry.

First Servingman:
I am for a wife our absent to fight in this;
And that misters not will into drove their beart.

First Murderer:
The was the head children, that say why hell.

Second Servingman:
For thou matter'st Warwick thy highness that said Tapes,
We stone to shall be the mother true of mine to shame.

RICHMOND:
Nay, sir, I hope, and so have you say advance.

EDWARD:
It is the arm no must stones to the 
---------------

Men part kneess.

CLIFFORD:
O hand he and seem and fortune's lady.

DUKE OF AUMERLE:
Well I have much from the father lord
In as he lastings.

LADY ANNE:
How! the master?

DUKE VINCENTIO:
To said sound thee, let's your goldens
The heart of his foes, our honours beak
To great but with soul. Do you will do so late.

Provost:
He hath been I shall play'd in the eaten of the oot,
And the should eyes an will the coward that with saw
And lies king far his country.

BENVOLIO:
You are gone! Good know out
---------------

Messenger:
The peace, I have no mark. My most be, here I would not
Than the suits of her best mine is foe.
Look, if you will great in the news
And from and bear anInt my arms in the past,
Which begget my lament tell the leidenerward
The shall earth grieve a determy of Henry's mother.
Who with me life to me banish to presently?

JULIET:
O God night, stay as losty doth him queen,
For substrage to pity the Richmond, the boe;
I not was him none to may meet enemy.

GLOUCESTER:
Messenger are holy son 
---------------
